ecost.com 2008-06-10

# eCost – Computers and Electronics for Home and Business – Plasma TV iPODS Laptop MP3 Player

Thank you for visiting eCOST.com! We have thousands of exciting computer products available at very low prices. We want your first buying experience to be a good one, so we have designed the following links to help ensure a smooth shopping experience!

  * Site Browser Requirements
  * Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)
  * Privacy Policy

  * return to "Help Desk"

* * *

**Having a problem shopping on the site?**

If you are having a shopping problem like the following: 

  * Unable to set up an account
  * Unable to put an item in your shopping cart
  * Unable to complete the checkout process
  * The browser crashes while using our site

Please check to see that you are running a recent browser version. Our site works best with the following browsers: 

  * Netscape v4.5 or higher
  * Internet Explorer v4.0 or higher
  * AOL v4.0 or higher

In addition, your browser must be enabled for: 

  * Cookies
  * Java Script
  * Security: Secure Socket Layer (SSL) v2.0 or higher
  * If you are shopping from behind a firewall, your proxy server must allow SSL communication through your firewall.

If the suggestions below do not solve the problem, please contact us at: webmaster@eCOST.com. Please tell us what step in the ordering process you were at, the time of day you experienced the problem, the browser (ex. Netscape, IE, AOL, etc.), and the version (ex. 4.5, 5.0, etc.) you are using. Thank you for shopping with us!

**Netscape v4.5+**

To enable cookies: 

  1. Edit
  2. Preferences
  3. Advanced
  4. Accept only cookies that get sent back to the originating server or accept all cookies (Check), then click OK.

To enable Java Scripting: 

  1. Edit
  2. Preferences
  3. Advanced
  4. Enable Java Script (Check), then click OK.

To enable SSL security: 

  1. Security Button
  2. Navigator
  3. Advanced Security (SSL) Configuration
  4. Enable SSL v2 and Enable SSL v3 (Check), then click OK.

**Internet Explorer v4.0**

To enable cookies: 

  1. View
  2. Internet Options
  3. Advanced
  4. Security
  5. Cookies
  6. Prompt before accepting cookies or Always accept cookies (Check), then click OK.

To enable Java Scripting: 

  1. View
  2. Internet Options
  3. Security
  4. Custom
  5. Settings
  6. Scripting
  7. Active Scripting
  8. Enable (Click), then click OK, then click OK again.

To enable SSL security: 

  1. View
  2. Internet Options
  3. Advanced
  4. Security
  5. Use SSL 2.0 and Use SSL 3.0 (Check), then click OK.

**Internet Explorer v5.0**

To enable cookies: 

  1. Tools
  2. Internet Options
  3. Security
  4. Internet
  5. Custom Level
  6. Cookies
  7. Allow Cookies
  8. Enable (Check), then click OK.

To enable Java Scripting: 

  1. Tools
  2. Internet Options
  3. Security
  4. Internet
  5. Custom Level
  6. Scripting
  7. Active Scripting
  8. Enable (Check), then click OK.

To enable SSL security: 

  1. View
  2. Internet Options
  3. Advanced
  4. Security
  5. Use SSL 2.0 and Use SSL 3.0 (Check), then click OK.

**AOL v4.0**

To enable cookies: 

  1. MyAOL
  2. Preferences
  3. WWW
  4. Security Settings
  5. Custom Levels
  6. Cookies
  7. Enable (Check), then click OK.

To enable Java Scripting: 

  1. MyAOL
  2. Preferences
  3. WWW
  4. Security Settings
  5. Custom
  6. Settings
  7. Scripting
  8. Active Scripting
  9. Enable (Check), then click OK.

To enable SSL security: 

  * Default setting is SSL 3.0.

**AOL v5.0**

To enable cookies: 

  1. MyAOL
  2. Preferences
  3. WWW
  4. Security Settings
  5. Custom Levels
  6. Cookies
  7. Enable (Check), then click OK.

To enable Java Scripting: 

  1. MyAOL
  2. Preferences
  3. WWW
  4. Security Settings
  5. Custom Levels
  6. Scripting
  7. Active Scripting
  8. Enable (Check), then click OK.

To enable SSL security: 

  * Default setting is SSL 3.0.

Because of the rarity of some products, eCOST.com may restrict the number of such items that you may purchase. It is eCOST.com’s policy to limit purchase quantities to 5 (of an item) per household or business within a four week period. If you have ordered more than this quantity, we will let you know whether we can accommodate your request. This information is subject to change. 

  1. How do I place an order?
  2. How can I check on my order? Track the package?
  3. Is it safe to pay online with eCOST.com?
  4. What is your privacy policy?
  5. What are my shipping options?
  6. What are my payment options?
  7. When do you charge sales tax?
  8. Can I cancel an order after it has been submitted?
  9. Can I return a product?
  10. How do I contact eCOST.com?

### How do I place an order?

We have two ways to order: online or over the phone with one of our sales representatives.

To place an order online, click on the  button of the item that you would like to purchase and then proceed through the online Checkout process.

To place an order over the phone, please call us at Toll Free 1 (877) 888-2678, option #1 during normal business hours and one of our sales professionals will be happy to assist you.

### How can I check on my order? Track the package?

There are two easy ways to check on your order: the first is to click on the Order Status button on the upper right of each page. Simply input your order number and shipping zip code, and the status of your order will be displayed.If your order was shipped with a carrier that provides tracking numbers (i.e. FedEx, UPS, etc.), then we will display the tracking number along with a link to the carrier’s site.Simply click on the link and the carrier’s site will provide up-to-date information re the status of your shipment.

Online Order Status is only available for our U.S. customers at this time. However, our Borderfree customers will receive tracking instructions in their shipment confirmation email for tracking their package in Canada, and our Customer Service team is also available to update you. 

The second method is to call our Customer Service team during normal business hours at Toll Free 1 (877) 888-2678, option #2, and we would be happy to update you over the phone.

Within 24 hours after your order ships, we will email you with a ship confirmation that lists which items have shipped, and the carrier and / or tracking number if available.

### Is it safe to pay online with eCOST.com?

Absolutely.We use the latest encryption technology called SSL and we are so confident that we guarantee 100% that your online transaction with us will be secure.

Please click here for a full description of our Security Guarantee.

### What is your privacy policy?

eCOST.com is very concerned about your privacy. Please click here for a full description of our Privacy Policy.

### What are my shipping options?

We offer a number of shipping options to best suit your delivery needs:

  * Ground – delivery in approximately 3 to 7 business days after shipment
  * 2nd Day – delivery in two business days after shipment
  * Standard Overnight – delivery the next business day afternoon after shipment
  * Priority Overnight – delivery the next business day morning after shipment
  * Overweight Priority – delivery in 2 to 5 business days after shipment on orders of 150lbs. or more

Borderfree Buyers:

  * Standard - delivery 5 to 14 days after shipment

Please click here for a complete description of our Shipping Methods.

### What are my payment options?

We offer a consumer finance plan via our eCOST.com Credit Card **Apply now!**.

We current accept the major credit cars such as VISA, MasterCard, Discover, American Express, Diners Club and Federal IMPAC, and VISA/MasterCard debit cards.

Borderfree Buyers are provided payment options through our partner, Borderfree which include Visa, American Express and Mastercard.

Unfortunately, we cannot accept open account orders, purchase orders, checks, COD, etc.

Please click here for more information on our Payment Options.

### When do you charge sales tax?

We charge sales tax on orders shipping into California, Texas and Tennessee.

Please click here for more information regarding Sales Tax.

For our Borderfree Buyers, all federal and provincial taxes (if applicable) are calculated for your order when you click on the “Borderfree Checkout” button.

### Can I cancel an order after it has been submitted?

You can usually cancel an order within an hour of order placement during normal business hours. Beyond that timeframe, it is very difficult for us to cancel orders due to the rapid transfer of orders in our supply chain. The exception to this rule is that we are able to cancel orders that have been backordered.

If you would like to cancel an order, please call us Toll Free at 1 (877) 888-2678 or email us at [cancel@ecost.com](mailto:cancel@ecost.com). We will try our best to cancel the order, but cannot guarantee that we will able to depending upon where the order is at in the credit approval, pick and ship processes.

Please click here for a complete description of our Order Cancellations policy.

### Can I return a product?

Generally, most products can be returned within 30 days of shipment.Very important return policies and procedures exist, however, and we would encourage you to familiarize yourself with our return policies and procedures prior to ordering.

Please click here for a complete description of our Return Policies and Procedures.

### How do I contact eCOST.com?

We are available by phone, email and/or US Mail. Please click **here** for the complete Contact options.

We look forward to hearing from you!

top /\

* * *

ECOST Privacy Policy  
_Last Revised: **February 23, 2005**_

We at ECOST (“ECOST”, “we” or “us”) understand that making purchases online involves a great deal of trust on your part. We take that trust seriously, and, as a result, we seek to ensure the security and confidentiality of your personal information online. This privacy policy is an effort to answer your privacy-related questions. If you have questions that are not addressed herein, please submit them to us by sending an email to [ webmaster@eCOST.com](mailto:webmaster@ecost.com).

The purpose of this privacy policy (the "Policy") is to help you understand what kinds of personally identifiable information we may gather about you when you visit the ECOST Web site located at [www.eCOST.com](http://www.ecost.com/) and related sub-domains (the “Site”), how we may use that information, whether we will disclose it, and how you can correct or update it. We note that this Policy sets forth our online information collection and use policies under U.S. law. The Site is intended for use by residents of the U.S. who are over the age of 18. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children (that is, minors younger than thirteen years of age). 

If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, you should not use the Site. We reserve the right to update or modify this Policy from time to time, and such changes to the Policy will be effective immediately; therefore please bookmark this page and review it periodically to assure familiarity with the most current version of the Policy. You can tell if the Policy has been updated since you last reviewed it by checking the "Last Revised" date at the beginning of the Policy. 

This Policy is the sole authorized statement of ECOST's practices with respect to the online collection of personally identifiable information and the usage of such information. Any summaries of this Policy generated by third party software or otherwise (for example, in connection with the "Platform for Privacy Preferences" or "P3P") shall have no legal effect, are in no way binding upon ECOST, shall not be relied upon in substitute for this Policy, and neither supersede nor modify this Policy.

To assist you with your review of our Policy, we have provided answers to questions that you may find important:

  *  What Personal Information We Collect 
  *  How We Use the Personal Information We Collect
  *  Marketing Communications: Opting Out
  *  Cookies
  *  Web Beacons
  *  How We Protect Your Personal Information
  *  Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences
  *  Other Information We Collect
  *  Advertisers
  *  Sweepstakes and Promotions
  *  Co-branded Sites: Links to Other Sites
  *  Online vs. Offline Practices
  *  Contacting ECOST

**What Personal Information We Collect**

ECOST collects personally identifiable information that you specifically and voluntarily provide on the Site or by email to ECOST. Personally identifiable information (“PII”) is information that identifies you as a specific individual, for example, your name, company name, account number, physical or email address, and phone number plus other information that personally identifies you including your industry, the number of employees at your company, and purchase history. The Site includes both public areas, open to all visitors, and private areas that are open only to those visitors who choose to register. In addition, visitors can sign up on the Site to request email newsletters and other information from ECOST. ECOST collects PII from you when you: 

  * Make a purchase 
  * Create an account 
  * Contact a phone sales representative 
  * Are contacted by a phone sales representative 
  * Subscribe to our newsletter 
  * Request a catalog 
  * Participate in a survey 
  * Register at our website

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp).

Return to Top

**How We Use the Personal Information We Collect**

We use the PII that you provide to us in order to 1) fulfill requests for products, services and/or information, 2) provide customer service, 3) offer new products or services, 4) measure and improve the effectiveness of our Site and our marketing endeavors, 5) tailor our online offerings to your preferences, 6) administer promotions or surveys, and 7) achieve other business purposes as permitted under applicable law.

When you make a purchase on our Site we collect credit card information including card number, card type, cardholder name and billing address, and expiration date, in order to bill you for purchases made through ECOST. Please review our Credit Card Policy for additional information.

ECOST may disclose PII to consultants, professional advisors and contractors who perform services on our behalf, but only to the extent necessary for them to perform such services. At times, ECOST may seek to validate the PII we have collected via an audit by a third party designed to determine the accuracy of and/or to update the information collected. We may also combine data that we collect online with data collected offline (such as through purchases made through one of our catalogs), or with data provided by other parties.

ECOST shares PII collected from our visitors and customers with our affiliated or related companies, including its parent company, affiliates, subsidiaries, or its parent company’s other subsidiaries.  
ECOST reserves the right to release PII concerning any visitor when that visitor is believed by ECOST to be in violation of any published guidelines for the use of the Site, or participates (or is suspected of participating) in any illegal or potentially illegal activity. ECOST also reserves the right to disclose PII to comply with applicable law, in response to civil subpoenas or discovery requests, or when we believe in good faith that disclosure is required to protect the rights, property, safety or security of ECOST, our visitors or the public, or to respond to an emergency.

In the event that we sell or otherwise transfer to a third party assets related either (a) to the Site or (b) to one or more of our businesses, divisions or affiliated companies, we reserve the right to also transfer any and all information (including any PII) associated with the Site and/or any business, division or affiliated company to such third party. However, all PII transferred to such third party shall be transferred subject to the usage restrictions contained in ECOST’s privacy policy. Please note that we are not responsible for retracting your PII from any third parties with whom we have shared your information pursuant to the terms of this Policy.

Return to Top

**Marketing Communications: Opting Out**

When you provide PII to us, including when registering to receive email newsletters, catalog subscriptions or other information, or to make a purchase, ECOST provides you with the opportunity to opt-out of having your information used for marketing communications. Unless you have opted out of receiving such communications, ECOST may use your PII to forward you, via email or mail, advertisements concerning ECOST products, services, special promotions, surveys or other opportunities from ECOST that we think may be of interest to you. Such email advertisements may also concern third party companies’ products and services, including companies in industries such as hardware and software, and other providers of the types of products that are sold or featured on the Site. 

ECOST has partnered with third parties to offer our customers and Site visitors a variety of products and services. Other than as set forth herein, we will not sell or lease your email address to third party advertisers to solicit you directly. However ECOST may share PII (such as your physical mailing address - but not your email address) with our marketing partners in order for them to offer you additional products and services that ECOST believes may be of interest to you. Although we only work with third parties whom we believe to be reputable, our marketing partners may have different privacy policies and practices than ECOST. We encourage you to review our marketing partners’ privacy policies to further understand their procedures for collecting, using and disclosing your information. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of our marketing partners or any other third parties. If you decide that you would like to discontinue receiving promotional materials from these or any third parties, please contact them directly.

Should you wish to change your preferences regarding the information that you receive from ECOST or its affiliates, or would prefer that we not share PII with our marketing partners, please refer to the paragraph below entitled “Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences.” Please note that we are not responsible for retracting your PII from any third parties with whom we have shared your information pursuant to the terms and conditions of this Policy.

Return to Top

**Cookies**

Upon visiting our Site we will assign you a unique ID in the form of a "cookie". A cookie is a piece of information that our server places on your computer’s hard drive, which ECOST may associate with your PII when you log on to the site. Cookies are used for such purposes as facilitating and personalizing your shopping and ordering experience, keeping track of your shopping basket during your visit, helping diagnose problems with our server, and administering our Site. We may use the information collected through cookies for marketing purposes to inform you of special offers, better understand your needs or answer your questions.  NOTE: You can control how and whether cookies will be accepted by your web browser, and you may remove them from your computer at any time at your discretion.

Return to Top

**Web Beacons**

Some ECOST Web pages and HTML-formatted e-mail newsletters may use Web beacons to compile aggregate statistics about website usage. A Web beacon is an electronic image, often called a single-pixel (1x1) or clear GIF, that is ordinarily not visible to the site visitor. Web beacons can recognize certain types of information on a visitor's computer, such as a visitor's cookie number, time and date of a page or image view, and a description of the page where the Web beacon is placed. When used in an e-mail, they can tell us whether an e-mail has been opened. 

Return to Top

**How We Protect Your Personal Information**

To help ensure the confidentiality of your PII, ECOST seeks to use security technology and procedures, which are reviewed periodically. We use encryption technology and Secure Socket Layers (“SSL”) in all areas where your personal and account information is required. This means that the personal information you submit to us via our Site is encrypted by your computer, and then decrypted again on our side, discouraging others from accessing your private information during transmission. If your browser does not support SSL, or if you are unable to establish a secure connection due to a company firewall, please call us at (877) 888-2678 to place your order by phone.

In addition, your personal, account information, and transaction history are kept behind our firewall.

Return to Top

**Correcting/Updating Your Personal Information and Preferences**

If you would like to have your PII removed from ECOST’s databases, or to make changes to your PII or to your preferences regarding the use of your PII for marketing purposes, please  click here. We will use reasonable efforts to comply with your request. Please note that we may need to contact you in order to be sure that we are updating the appropriate information. When requesting that PII be updated or that your preferences be changed, please keep in mind that until the change is implemented, you may still receive email and/or physical mailings from us. Furthermore, there will be residual information that will remain within ECOST databases, access logs and other records, which may contain such PII. The residual information will not be used for commercial purposes; however, ECOST reserves the right, from time to time, to recontact former customers or visitors to the Site. Please note that we are not responsible for retracting your PII from third parties with whom we have shared your information pursuant to the terms and conditions of this Policy.

Return to Top

**Other Information We Collect**

_Information About Your Computer and Your Site Activities:_ When a visitor comes to our Site we collect and aggregate information about the visitor’s computer (such as its IP address, operating system and browser software), and click-stream information (such as the address (or “URL”) of the Web site that the visitor came from before visiting our Site, which pages of the Site were visited, the order in which they were visited and which hyperlinks were clicked) for the purpose of assessing our Site traffic and the effectiveness of our Site content, as well as to help diagnose problems with our servers. This data allows us to improve the quality of your visit by streamlining your ability to navigate the Site, and to develop featured programs and content that will be of interest to our customers and Site visitors. 

_Aggregated Information:_ ECOST may collect and aggregate demographic information about our Site visitors. For example, we may seek to aggregate information regarding the gender make-up, average age and range of income levels of Site visitors in order to better service our user community. We may use such information in its aggregated form without restriction. 

_Information About Corporate and Other Organizational Customers:_ We may collect information pertaining solely to corporations, governmental or educational entities, or other business or not for profit entities, such as, for example, a company's address. We may use any such corporate information without restriction. In an effort to better support our customers by delivering more relevant marketing communications, ECOST will, on occasion, purchase third party information about businesses and other entities that are our customers. The company information we purchase may include number of employees, or annual sales volume and company structure. This is used to customize such customers’ online/offline experience and to supplement our internal sales information to better serve you. 

Return to Top

**Advertisers**

ECOST may use outside advertising companies ("Advertisers") to serve advertisements on the Site. Please be advised that such Advertisers may use cookies or other technologies to enable such Advertisers to record which ads your browser has seen, and which Site pages you may have been viewing when the ads were delivered. 

Return to Top

**Sweepstakes and Promotions**

We may from time to time offer sweepstakes, contests, or other similar promotions on the Site. Additional PII may be required in order to participate in such promotions, so that we may, for example, verify entrants' eligibility and identity and notify winners. Participation in such promotions is completely voluntary. If and when we sponsor such promotions, we will post relevant privacy information in the respective "official rules" and/or registration areas for such promotions. That privacy information, to the extent it conflicts with this Policy, will govern that particular sweepstakes, contest or promotion—please remember to read it carefully.

Other companies may offer sweepstakes, contests or similar promotions through our Site, including through the Rebates & Coupons page. ECOST is not responsible for any such promotions offered by third parties. Please read all related terms and conditions carefully, or contact the applicable third party for more information. The collection and use of personal information in connection with such promotions is governed by such third party’s privacy policy, and not by the policies of ECOST.

Return to Top

**Co-branded Sites: Links to Other Sites**

The Site offers certain features that are provided and/or hosted by third parties, but that may be presented on pages displaying ECOST’s branding. For example, ECOST-branded pages featuring investor relations information about ECOST may be created and operated by a third party data provider specializing in such information. The Site may also contain links to other Web sites, or other affiliated sites (e.g., event sponsors, or companies offering rebates or other promotions through our Rebates & Coupons page). We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any such Web sites, including such sites’ use of any information (such as IP number, browser type or operating system) collected when visitors to the Site click through links to those sites. Even though such information might not identify you personally, we strongly encourage you to become familiar with the privacy practices of any third party sites.

Return to Top

**Online vs. Offline Practices**

Please note that this Policy applies solely to our online information-gathering and dissemination practices in connection with the Site, and does not apply to any of our practices conducted offline other than as expressly set forth in this Policy. 

Return to Top

**Contacting ECOST**

Should you have any questions, please e-mail us at [ webmaster@eCOST.com](mailto:webmaster@ecost.com)

**The eCOST.com Privacy Policy**

At eCOST.com, Inc. we are committed to protecting your privacy online. Our Privacy Policy demonstrates our firm commitment to protecting the privacy of our customers. We use the information that we collect about our customers to fulfill product and service purchases and to create a more personalized online experience.

When you shop at eCOST.com, we collect transactional information, or Personally Identifiable Information, from you such as your name, telephone number, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, credit card or other payment information and a password. eCOST.com does not sell or rent your transactional information to others without your prior consent. eCOST.com uses customer information only for the purposes of filling orders, contacting purchasers to inform them of their order status, sending promotional information, and enhancing the user experience. 

eCOST.com uses cookies to help identify you when you visit the site. The cookies contain randomly assigned user identification numbers, the country where you are located, and your name to welcome you back to the site. The cookies make your use of the site easier, allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the site run more smoothly and help us to maintain a secure site. Cookies MUST be enabled on your system to shop at eCOST.com.

eCOST.com will occasionally offer special contests and promotions. When you enter a contest or other promotion, we may ask you for contact information such as your name, address and e-mail address in order to administer the contest, to send you promotional e-mails, notify winners and make the winners' list publicly available pursuant to certain states' laws. Your consent to such promotional use and disclosure of this information is a condition of your participation.

At eCOST.com you can be assured that your transactional information is secure, consistent with current industry standard SSL encryption technology. The importance of security for all transactional information associated with our customers is of utmost concern to us. Our secure servers protect the information using state of the art firewall technology. All customer transactional account information is kept on a secure server. 

Please be aware that our site may contain advertisements and links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by the eCOST.com Privacy Policy. eCOST.com has no control over the use or disclosure of user data on other sites on the Internet and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of such sites to determine your privacy rights on such sites. 

eCOST.com will remain committed to protecting your privacy online. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time. When such a change is made, we will post the revised Privacy policy on our website so please bookmark this page and check back periodically. Any changes, corrections or updates to your transactional information can be edited during the purchase process. Questions regarding the eCOST.com Privacy Policy should be directed to [comments@eCOST.com](mailto:comments@eCOST.com) or may also be sent directly to the following address: 

> eCOST.com, Inc.  
>  Attn: Privacy Policy Compliance  
>  2555 W.190th St.  
>  Torrance, CA 90504  
>
